Action/Platform Game

Content:
Main character has gone to the world of insanity by mistake. Now he is trying to find a way back to the real world.

Hidden content (dev only):
While the theme is escaped the insanity, the stages show the further player goes, the deeper he/she is into it:
	+ Gradually show less signs of human (Enemy less and less humanoid, etc);
	+ Gradually become harder;
	+ BG: Gradually switchs to space;
	+ Humanoid enemies gradually become disturbing, to the point they look more insane than non-humanoid enemies;
	+ Stages gradually become shorter and more intense.
There are a number of stage categorized into 4 phases in order:
	+ Edge of insanity:
		Presents the attitudes of people toward alien things (idea/ideal/standard);
		Aggressive humanoid enemies (soldier) attacks/pursue player if he/she comes near.
	+ World of the rejected:
		Presents things that left by human;
		Enemies (fetus/ orphan) present things that were discarded, were not nurtured, things abandoned by human;
		As their abandonments are necessary for human to reach this point, their presence alone can harm human
			=> no need to attack/pursue, just touching can harm player;
		Orphans may run toward player as they are capable of desiring a different life/ reality.
		This phase should have the strongest impression.	
	+ Sea of stars:
		Void space with no sign of life;
		Strengthening the feeling of loneliness;
		Through each stage, player gradually becomes bigger compared to the planet/platform. 
	+ World tower:
		Mecha theme;
		Represent the edge of humanity, the furthest point human has reached in this universe (Voyager 1);
		Short but intense section where player is constantly under attack by non-living enemies;
		The end is when the player reach and play the golden disk.
Some suggestion:
	Distinguish between living and non-living enemies with a special fickle light presenting heartbeat.
	Player may call for help from an omnipotent god which will annihilate any enemies on screen
		+ The price is that the player will sink deeper into insanity for each contact (extend phase 3 for each use of power).
		 